# **Trinh Gliedt**

510-396-6601 | Fremont, California | chuot2008@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Github

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a solution seeker who fell in love with coding, and I have an undying curiosity about all things tech. I love tackling complex technical problems and devising elegant, efficient solutions that impact people's everyday lives.

I come from a non-traditional coding background. I have degrees in Environmental Engineering in Vietnam, and then moved to the United States to study Business. I'm also a CPA with an active license. I have spent the last 9 years in the accounting world, during which time I honed a meticulous and efficient approach to solving complex problems, as well as customer-facing and collaboration skills.

I'm all about optimizing systems (another skill I developed while accounting!), so when I saw the opportunity at a prior job to eliminate a repetitive process and save the team a bunch of time, I jumped on it! I self-taught programming skills in Excel, and wrote a program that saved our team a ridiculous number of man hours.

This was one of the experiences that helped me discover my passion for coding and start down the path to becoming a software developer. I joined Coding Dojo Bootcamp and have learned 3 full stacks within 14 weeks (Python, MERN and Java). Coding Dojo is a highly collaborative learning environment where I built functional and responsive applications in dynamic, small-team settings.

# **MY PORTFOLIO**

http://trinhgliedt.com/

# **CERTIFICATION**

Amazon Web Service Certified Cloud Practitioner. See credentials.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

MERN (Node, React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose), Redux, Python (Django, Bcrypt, SQLite), JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap, GitHub, Postman, VSCode, API, Java, Eclipse (Spring Boot, MySQL), AWS (EC2), Google Firebase, WordPress

## TECHNICAL PROJECTS

PreSense | Full stack development

2020

- A Covid diagnosis tool based on user's input
  - Designed the front end and back end for a project partnering with a medical institution that could help health professionals treating COVID or potential COVID patients.

Tech Stack: Javascript/React/Google Firebase/Google Firestore. Deployed on Google Cloud.

**Sunflowers** | <u>GitHub</u> | Full stack development | <u>Link to site</u> *An online clothing shop that makes shopping easier for families* 

2020

- Tech Stack: Python/Django/Sqlite. Deployed on AWS EC2.
- Designed 12 user friendly HTML templates using Bootstrap, pagination and conditional rendering logic with Jinja
  for customer usage and owner usage, including product browsing, product details, shopping cart checkout,
  inventory upload and accounting view.
- Configured SQLite database models using Django framework, Bcrypt and email RegEx validation to enable saving orders and allow storing users information securely.
- Utilized Django admin tool to allow creation of product categories and uploading of product information and product images.
- Constructed page routing and back-end logic using Python to execute customer shopping functions and owner functions.

EquityX | GitHub

Helping companies and investors manage their cap tables, valuation, investments, and equity plans

- Tech Stack: Javascript/React.
- Constructed seamless information flow between different components.
- Designed sticky menu bar and pop up contact form. Implemented responsive design to ensure components fit
  nicely in different screen sizes.

AQI Maps | GitHub

A single page application displaying real time Air Quality Index (AQI) on Google Maps

- Tech stack: Javascript/React.
- Retrieved information from 2 application programming interfaces, Google Maps API and World Air Quality Index API (WAPI), overlaid WAPI on maps API using Javascript and Bootstrap in React framework to provide users a clear visualization of air quality index by location.
- Identified user's current location using Google Geolocation API and Google Geocode API to display relevant information to their location upon their consent and to search by address or landmark.
- Architected database with MongoDB and integrated Bcrypt to securely store user data securely.
- Functionalized logic using Javascript in React to filter out relevant data and format information for a clear presentation of AQI values to users.
- Collaborated with project teammates using GitHub branches and git pull, add, commit, push, merge, stash.

# Let's Meet | GitHub | Full stack development

2020

A event organization tool that helps connect people with mutual interests

- Tech stack: Java/Spring Boot/MySQL.
- Designed JSP views using Bootstrap, pagination and conditional rendering logic for events listing, event creation and editing.
- Configured MySQL database models using Spring Boot framework, Bcrypt and Spring Boot validation to enable
  users to create and edit events and allow storing users information securely.
- Utilized Django admin tool to allow creation of product categories and uploading of product information and product images.
- Implemented seamless chat functionality with Sockets, Thymeleaf and Webjar for intuitive real-time communication.
- Collaborated with project teammates using GitHub branches and git pull, add, commit, push, merge, stash.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Full Stack Developer | Coding Dojo | Remote | Volunteer

2020 - 2021

 Designed the front end and back end for a project partnering with a medical institution that could help health professionals treating COVID or potential COVID patients.

## Accounting Manager | Pacific Urban Residential | Palo Alto, CA

2017-2020

 Managed 4 senior accountants, consolidated a portfolio of over \$1B, researched and provided guidance to staff on new business, streamlined processes with external contractors, and directly serviced equity partners. Designed and implemented excel macro tool that sped up consolidation process and reduced errors for the extended team.

## Senior Accountant | Pacific Urban Residential | Palo Alto, CA

2015-2017

• Fulfilled accounting, budgeting and financial reportings for up to 15 properties of 100 to 500 units each. Voluntarily prepared procedures and process improvement suggestions that uniformed new hire training.

## Senior Accountant/Auditor | Allen & Cook, Inc. | San Jose, CA

2013-2015

 Performed accounting and auditing for over 50 clients. Originated a new automated budgeting method that reduced processing time.

EDUCATION	
<ul> <li>Coding Dojo   Full-Stack Developer Certificate   Online</li> <li>Immersive Full-Stack Training Program in HTML, Python, MERN and Java.</li> </ul>	2020
Northwestern Polytechnic University   Master of Business Administration   Fremont, CA	2010
Ho Chi Minh University of Technology   BS in Environmental Engineering   Vietnam	2007

2011-2013

Accounting Supervisor | Better Bookkeepers | San Jose, CA